and all right Manisha thank you so much
for the updates there from the commodity
Universe back to equities right now by
the way some of the hidani group stocks
ACC and ambuja are well off their
morning highs let's just revisit that
story on the group The promoters of the
group looking to Pare down their pledges
Vivek
well absolutely right uh you know as you
mentioned you know there has been a bit
of profit booking from the top uh
however you know revisiting the story in
a statement to the media last evening
what they mentioned was that the adani
group has fully prepaid shareback
promoter financing and you know what
they're saying is that they have now
concluded the full prepayment of margin
link shareback financing so most of the
promoter pledges that were further
invoked you know both the sharp
decreases while the share prices were
concerned has now been prepaid now what
they've also done is they've gone ahead
and increased Equity as far as Abuja
financing is concerned by prepaying
almost 500 million US dollars as you
know the stated intent to reduce sponsor
level leverage now what happened is that
so far the promoters have infused 2.6
billion dollars out of the total
acquisition value of 6.6 billion dollars
for ambuja as well as ACC so now the
entire prepayment program of 2.65
billion dollars has been completed
within six weeks remember on March 8th 2
the company or the group had prepaid
close to 7 1374 crore worth of shareback
financing
all right thanks a lot for that so adani
group all of those stocks are seeing a
big relief rally this morning but I see
I say Lombard is the other one on our
radar if you're wondering why surbi has
more details on this we'll be over to
you
hi thanks for that so I say Lombard is
moving in trade today and that is
because ICICI Bank has said that RBI has
approved its request for an extension
until September 9 2024 which was earlier
September 2023 to reduce its stake in
icsa Lombard to less than 30 percent now
as per December 2022 disclosures icsa
bank has a stake of 48 in ICICI Lombard
now following Lombard's acquisition of
bharti AXA ICICI Bank stake fell below
50 and it was required by the regulator
to reduce its stake to less than 30
percent now in September 2020 the
regulator had given ICICI Bank three
years to comply with this regulation
which has now been extended by one more
year Morgan Stanley says that while the
extension provides time to execute what
is relatively a large stake sale the
duration of the extension being only one
year makes it unlikely to result in any
durable relief rally in the stock
oh